flipdog.com 2013-05-20

# Privacy

**Overview**

FlipDog.com is committed to respecting the privacy of our users. We strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to the FlipDog.com Web Site and does not apply to information we collect in any other fashion.

The information gathered on FlipDog.com may be shared within FlipDog.com and its affiliated companies on a worldwide basis in order to deliver the products and services we offer to employers such as searches for job seekers or in order to undertake analysis of our database such as aggregate profiling of our users. "Affiliated companies" means entities that control, are controlled by or are under common control with FlipDog.com. The FlipDog.com site contains links to other Web sites over which we have no control. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to which you choose to link from our Site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.

**Other Uses of Information**

We also share aggregated anonymous information about visitors to FlipDog.com with its clients, partners and other third parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to the FlipDog.com site and how those visitors use the FlipDog.com site.

**Use of Cookies**

We use "cookies" to help personalize and maximize your online experience and time online. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize FlipDog.com pages, or register for services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information (such as user name, password and preferences). Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized site experience. When you return to FlipDog.com , the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized. We also use cookies to track click streams and for load balancing. You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline all cookies if you prefer. Alternatively, you may be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on FlipDog.com.

**Use of Web Beacons**

FlipDog.com may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information; they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our Web site usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. You may not decline web beacons, however, they can be rendered ineffective by declining all cookies or modifying your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis.

Third parties are not permitted to use Web beacons on the FlipDog.com site.

**Children**

The FlipDog.com site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.

**Changes to Privacy Statement**

If we decide to materially change our Privacy Statement for FlipDog.com, we will post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it. If at any time, you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Statement or believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Statement, please feel free to contact us. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly answer your question or resolve your problem.

**Contact Information**

FlipDog.com is the name under which Monster Worldwide, a Delaware corporation with its principal place of business at 5 Clock Tower Place, Maynard, MA 01754 does business. Monster Worldwide is the legal entity that determines the purposes and means of processing the information gathered at FlipDog.com

_FlipDog and Monster encourage you to[be safe](http://help.monster.com/besafe/) when applying to jobs online._

Thank you for using FlipDog.com.

Return to FlipDog home page
